export const Questions = [
  {
    question: 'Everything in React is a __________',
    options: ['Module', 'Component', 'Hooks', 'Template'],
    correctAnswer: 'Component',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?',
    options: ['Original DOM', 'Virtual DOM', 'Both A & B', 'None Of The Above'],
    correctAnswer: 'Virtual DOM',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following acts as the input of a class-based component?',
    options: ['Class', 'Factory', 'Render', 'Props'],
    correctAnswer: 'Props',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is ReactJs?',
    options: [
      'Server side framework ',
      'A Library for building interaction interfaces ',
      'Client Side Framework ',
      'None of the Above',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A Library for building interaction interfaces ',
  },
  {
    question: 'React is ............ Javascript library ',
    options: [
      'Module based',
      'Component based',
      'System based',
      'All are correct',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Component based',
  },
  {
    question: 'A valid react component can return ...... number of elements. ',
    options: ['1', '2', '3', 'None of the Above'],
    correctAnswer: '1',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following API is a MUST for every ReactJS component? ',
    options: ['getInitialState', 'render', 'renderComponent', 'None'],
    correctAnswer: 'renderComponent',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the default port for webpack dev server? ',
    options: ['3000', '8080', '3306', '8809'],
    correctAnswer: '8080',
  },
  {
    question: 'React Js is developed by ',
    options: ['Google', 'Microsoft', 'Facebook', 'None of the Above'],
    correctAnswer: 'Facebook',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following is a correct definition of state in react? ',
    options: [
      'A persistent storage ',
      'An internal data store (object) of component',
      'Both',
      'None',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'An internal data store (object) of component',
  },
];
